# **Connor David Frasier**

#### Summary

Highly motivated & accountable creative professional with proven marketing skills and a passion for gaining more knowledge. Over 4 years of experience working with many departments in higher education, from content brainstorming & creation to managing student employees. Looking to use & grow my skill set in a new environment where I can make a significant impact

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Clarkson University, Potsdam, NY - Digital Content Creator & Writer

April 2019 - Present

- Lead University Videographer
  - Using leadership skills in creation, storyboarding, producing, and editing all video projects with clients throughout various university departments
  - Communicate with the marketing department to plan the best tactics for video production
  - The most notable production was Clarkson's Official Campus Tour, with 10K views
  - A recent video series campaign received over 48K views on YouTube since April 2020
  - Created, shot & edited two of the most viewed videos on Clarkson's YouTube channel with a combined 30K views, 800 watch hours, and a 70% full retention rate
- Lead University Photographer
  - Photos used for magazines, websites, and other various digital strategies
  - Portraits, modeling photos, professional headshots, live events, drone photography
- Analyze social media statistics
  - 3x growth of initial YouTube subscriber count with 2.500 new subscribers since taking control of Clarkson channel in May 2019.
  - Average of over 18K views each month with 510 watch hours on Clarkson's YouTube
  - SEO strategies with titles, captions, and descriptions for videos with specific tagging and hashtags.
- Graphic design
  - Thumbnail & graphic creation for social media and email blasts, as well as graphic work for video intros and outros.
- Plan and execute various marketing campaigns
  - Working closely with various departments including admissions, alumni giving, and all educational departments as a team to grow exposure and engagement
  - Noteworthy campaigns are for the annual giving day, athletic giving day, and end-of-fiscal year summary.
- Utilize Adobe products in the creation of various forms of marketing
  - Daily use of Premiere Pro, After Effects, Illustrator, Photoshop & Indesign
- Managerial Duties
  - Supervisor of 3-5 student-employees each semester
  - Responsibilities included responding to marketing requests, scheduling events & projects for employees, oversight of project completion, & mentoring employees

## Allentown Tables/Fitch's Billiards, Easton, PA - Admin work/Laborer

2016-2019

- Installing pool and game tables
- Using teamwork skills to setup and install game tables for customers
- Website management/editing
- Administrative work

# Mackey Photo & Video, East Stroudsburg, PA - Creative Intern

2018

- Coordinating with clients for special events
- Produced and edited video & photographed events
- Created promotional videos and commercials

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Clarkson University, Potsdam, NY - MBA (in progress)

2020-Present

# East Stroudsburg University, East Stroudsburg, PA -B.S

2014-2018

- B.S in Digital Media Technologies
- 3.5 GPA

## **Additional Info**

Please visit my portfolio site below for creation examples

Portfolio Website: http://www.frasiermedia.com/

Linkedin Page: https://www.linkedin.com/in/connor-frasier-522944148/

YouTube Page: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCgvyZay66nfrmQEP70kG4ww